(Leonard:)Or we could mix things up.
Maybe pick names out of a hat, whatever.
(Penny:)Whoa, whoa, whoa.
(Penny:)Why don't you just admit you don't
want to be on a team with me.
I just said, "Couples sound great."
(Penny:)Mm-hmm, yeah, you don't
think I'm smart enough.
(Penny:)You think I'm gonna be a liability.
(Penny:)Even though I totally just used
the word "liability" correctly
(Penny:)in a sentence.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
No, let's do couples. I want to.
No, no, no. Let's mix things up.
(Penny:)I choose Sheldon,
and we're gonna kick your ass!
Yeah-- really?
(Sheldon:)The only time I'm ever
picked first for a team
(Sheldon:)and I'm stuck with the liability?
(Amy:)Stop that.
Penny is not a liability.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
Do you want to be on my team?
(Amy:)Maybe we pick names out of a hat.
(Penny:)Hurry up and close the door
so they can't hear us.
(Penny:)Would you stop pouting?
So, you picked my name. Get over it.